Edited & Resync By me # NAIM2007 #
What happened to your teddy bear?
This?
Well, my dad bought this bear
when I was three.
Not that I remember,
that's just what my mom said.
He bought it at a rest area
when we were going on a trip.
I've always...
Father bought this but that's not
the reason I've kept this bear.
Stuffed animals are hard
to throw in the trash, right?
They have eyes!
Does she have a name?
Yes.
Ku.
That's all.
She has a cute face, right?
The school...
Where are you?
Yamada?
I'm the engineer on the express train
There are pretty girls at every station
But when you only stop for three minutes
There's not enough time to kiss them
-Tokyo, Kyoto, Osaka
-Hey.
Yes?
You know the commercial
with Riho Makise in the sea?
Yes.
Apparently there's a woman's face
in the water.
-For real?
-For real.
It's the ghost of a drowned woman.
What? For real?
-Scary, right?
-Yes!
Apparently you can see it
if you pause the video.
-No way!
-It's true.
No way! Have you seen it, Takahashi?
-What, me?
-Yes.
I think I saw it.
-For real?
-Yes.
That's terrifying.
-It is, right?
-Yes!
-Wakakusa.
-Yes?
Can't you smell the sea?
There's a river in our town.
It's near the mouth of the river,
and the water spreads out and stagnates.
It smells bad.
Canada goldenrod grows near the river,
and you will often see dead cats
around the area.
NO TRESPASSING
Pochi!
Where are you?
Time to go home.
Pochi!
Been playing?
Oh, you have something.
Did you find something good?
What did you find?
Right.
Come on, Pochi.
Time to go.
Okay, Pochi!
Okay.
Let's go home.
Rumi!
That's Lancôme Définicils!
Yes.
I got a guy to buy it for me.
I wish my boyfriend was 38!
Ask Takahashi to buy you one.
Like that'll happen!
Yoshie!
Haruna! Was it all right yesterday?
Ugo Ugo Ruga
already ended when I got home.
My mom was so mad at me.
Oh, there's Kannonzaki.
What?
Morning!
I wonder how Kannonzaki and Haruna
are doing at the moment.
Don't ask me.
She keeps things to herself too much.
She didn't even say they were together.
Even though he's hot!
I can't stand Kannonzaki.
Haruna has no taste in guys.
-You asshole!
-It hurts.
-Yamada and the locker!
-What is it?
You're awful!
What?
How did you know?
-Yoshie told me.
-Takahashi?
It was terrible!
Pitch black, freezing cold...
-You went to help him?
-Of course, I did!
Do something like that again
and I'll kill you!
What?
Is there something between you and Yamada?
Don't be stupid!
It's Kanna Tajima.
Maybe she's looking for Yamada.
He's not here yet!
Hey.
-Morning.
Maybe the rumors aren't true.
-What?
-That Yamada's gay.
Someone saw him in Shinjuku,
holding hands with a boy.
And I heard he's with the freshman,
Kozue Yoshikawa.
You mean that model girl?
Apparently they went to the bushes
by the river together.
I bet you heard that from Takahashi.
Nothing he says is true.
Hey, that's mean!
-Stop it!
-Come to my place today.
Nobody's home.
In your dreams, dumbass!
Eat as much as you like.
You too, Punna.
Morning, Maru!
You must be sleepy.
What's the matter?
You have beautiful eyes, don't you?
Of the civil liberties,
there is freedom of conscience,
freedom of the body, and economic freedom.
Freedom of conscience means the freedom
to think and speak as you like.
Religious beliefs, gatherings of people,
means of expression,
learning and the likes are not
to be restricted by the state,
and individual freedom must be protected.
This principle
is based on the state's control
of Shinto before the war,
and its continuance is deeply cared about.
Now, freedom of expression...
Don't mess with me.
It means the right to give
your opinion to others...
Please tell us your name.
I'm Kannonzaki.
Nice to meet you.
How big is your family?
There's my dad, my mom,
my big bro, and me.
My close family.
Your close family?
My dad and mom aren't together.
I guess you could say
they don't care about each other.
She found out that he was cheating,
it's the same old story.
My mom got into dancing,
she did nothing else all week.
My dad and a woman from his office...
I say "woman", but she's about 45,
she's practically a granny.
They ran away together
around fall last year,
but they came back
after about a week in the end.
Things are normal now.
We all act as if nothing happened.
Does your girlfriend know
about your family?
No, I haven't talked to her about it.
Why not?
I don't think she'd be interested
in stuff like that,
and she only has her mom around,
so she might just envy me
for having two parents.
How did you two start seeing each other?
I guess it just felt right.
She gets really mad sometimes,
but she doesn't get too suspicious,
so she's easy to be with.
Keep your mouth shut!
Strip.
Strip what?
I told you to strip!
Strip!
-Haruna's skipping class!
-I have a headache.
I'm starving.
I bet you want that gross udon again.
-It's my favorite now!
-No way!
It's a paper blizzard!
Wow!
It's amazing!
ICHIRO YAMADA
-Freaky! You saw it?
-I think so.
For real?
-Hey!
-Where's Kannonzaki?
-He said he's skipping this afternoon.
-Where's Yamada?
-I don't know.
-You're lying!
What's this?
That guy's crazy.
We were just messing around.
What do you mean?
Do something.
It's something only a girlfriend can say.
Where's Yamada?
The old chemistry lab.
NO TRESPASSING
Yamada!
It's okay.
It's Wakakusa.
I brought your clothes. Where are you?
Over here.
Sorry, it happened again.
That's okay.
-Wakakusa.
-Yes?
Are you free tonight?
Yes.
I'll tell you about my secret treasure.
What?
I want you to see it.
The rate of the ozone layer depletion
went from 5% to 10% in the last 17 years.
The amount of fluorocarbon released
by humans into the atmosphere
is 15 million tons.
About 10% of this, 1.5 million tons,
reaches the stratosphere,
destroying the ozone layer.
MOM, I'M MEETING UP WITH A FRIEND,
THERE'S CURRY IN THE POT, HARUNA
Sorry!
It was my turn to cook dinner.
What were you like as a child?
When I was in elementary school,
I always go to the library.
I loved books about UFOs.
I've always wanted to see one.
I've been bullied since elementary school.
One day, I got beaten up badly.
My whole body was black and blue,
and I couldn't let my parents find out.
Having your parents find out is the worst.
So...
I didn't want to go home.
I looked up at the sky from the roof
of the apartment block till it got dark.
I kept wishing for a UFO to appear.
I think I was up there for a few hours.
I still feel a strong desire
to see one from time to time.
It doesn't have to be a UFO.
I guess...
I want to see something totally
different from the reality to appear.
Hello, Koyama residence.
Phone for you. Some boy named Kannonzaki.
Okay.
No more long calls.
Mom said you're costing her--
Okay.
What is it?
What?
That was so cruel.
Everyone hates me.
That's not true.
I bet some of the girls like you.
They think you're cute or mysterious--
I'm nothing nice like that.
I want to gut the people
who treat me like a worm,
turn their skin inside out, salt it,
and feed it to dogs.
I want to put trash into the mouths
of the girls who watch and laugh.
That's all I ever think about.
I'm a homosexual.
You can call me gay, faggot,
pervert, or whatever.
But aren't you seeing Tajima from Class B?
That's just an act.
Does Tajima know that?
No.
It's not fair for her, really.
You're the first normal person
I've ever spoken to, Wakakusa.
Is it really all right?
It's okay.
My mom's at dance class,
and my dad's on a business trip.
Plus I'll be pissed
if we can't do it today.
So selfish.
Says the girl who came
after one phone call.
Hurry up and get it out.
You're kidding, a snake? No, it's not...
It's somewhere around here.
What?
-Here it is.
-What?
Do you do this kind of thing
with Haruna, too?
Shut up. It's none of your business.
I found it last year.
I'd been beaten up like I was today.
It's embarrassing, so I came here to cry.
Then I saw this.
-Did you tell the police?
-I really should, but...
Around fall last year,
there was still flesh on the bone.
There we go.
I...
don't know if I'm dead or alive...
but looking at it gives me courage.
No, I'll die...
I'll die...
Another person knows about this.
Who?
Kozue Yoshikawa.
The freshman?
When I came at the end of last year,
she was already here.
Since then, we sometimes come together.
It's her treasure, too.
How long have you been doing
this kind of work?
Maybe since I was about three.
I wasn't a model at the start,
I was more like a child actor.
I did things like dramas
and TV commercials.
My parents are in that line of work,
so they asked if I wanted to try doing it.
But as for the work itself,
everyone comes together to make one thing
which I think is great.
When you do magazine work,
you work with photographers
and all kinds of people.
And there are more brilliant people
when you do TV work.
But you'll get a sense that
it doesn't have to be you right there.
Anyone could do it.
You think that anyone could do it?
I think I look gross when I see
a magazine or something I'm in.
I wonder why they keep using me
with an ugly face,
yet compliment me.
But I don't believe them.
I'm sure the truth
is that they don't really mean it,
and they're just saying
what they think they have to say.
Like they're pleased with themselves
for calling an ugly person beautiful.
How is school? Do you enjoy it?
Compared to work, school feels genuine.
Genuine?
I don't know if the people at school
call things as they are,
but I'm sure that if they think
something is ugly, they'll say it.
They'll at least say it behind your back.
-You mean everyone is honest?
-Yes.
How are you feeling, Yoshikawa?
I'll go to my next class.
That won't do.
You need to have a balanced diet.
Your health comes before work.
Yes, Nurse.
So older students skip class a lot, too.
Do you have enough credits?
I miss school for work a lot,
so I only have just enough.
Oh, look.
The one who just threw the ball.
Running towards the center.
Yes!
That's the guy Yamada likes.
What?
That boy...
He is Yamada's other treasure.
I wear my navy uniform
I'm a Tokyo bus girl
-Hey.
-Yes?
The old lady with makeup
from the apartment near school...
Yes?
She dries her see-through,
lace purple panties on the balcony.
That old lady has taken the cherries
of countless boys at our school.
For real?
Why don't you ask her?
How old is she, though?
-Ask that after.
-Okay.
Oh, something's biting!
-You idiot.
-Shit!
-You were saying?
-Right.
-You know the river behind the school?
-Yes?
Well, there...
Excuse me!
Hey!
Have you heard?
The old man died, his money is buried,
and we might...
-What are you talking about?
-So, anyway!
There's a cabin in the bushes,
near the river behind the school.
An old man lived there, right?
He was evicted and he moved
to a different apartment,
but he recently died.
He was broke when he died,
but he has a lot of money stashed away!
Really?
And guess what!
The money is buried in the bushes!
-The bushes?
-Right!
Ten million in the bushes!
Isn't it amazing?
One second, I just...
Haruna!
-How much is it?
-140 yen.
Is Yoshikawa around?
Yoshikawa?
She was here earlier, but...
She often disappears.
What?
Ten million!
What can you do with that?
-Where's Haruna?
-She went off somewhere.
Right.
I can make my dreams come true!
Ten million yen!
Why did you bring me here?
I'm mad at you.
Why?
Maybe I'll tell Haruna about everything.
What?
How you tied my hands and feet,
blindfolded me,
and stuck a can of mousse
in both of my holes!
You little...
Hey!
I'm only kidding.
Hey...
Shall we do it here?
-Do you want 100 million yen?
-Yes!
-Do you want to be filthy rich?
‫ !Money-‬
‫ Money-‬
-What a bunch of idiots!
‫ !Money-‬
All I said was that there might
be money buried there.
What? It's not true?
My mom went to the old man's funeral,
and she wondered
if he might have buried it.
What?
What about the 150 million?
Where did you get that from?
Is that true, Takahashi?
All right, let's go!
-Let's go!
Wait!
It's not true!
Hey!
The money's a lie!
It's a lie!
It's a lie! Hey!
It's not true! Hey!
Haruna!
Where are you going?
Those little punks.
Hey. Where are you going?
-Come on.
-Hey.
I'll tell you about my secret treasure.
Sorry.
I thought this would really suit you.
You seem like a blue kind of guy.
I didn't get you anything
for your birthday.
We've only started dating in December,
and your birthday's in March.
Thank you.
Do you want to go
to the aquarium on Hakkeijima?
I still haven't been there.
Sure.
I'll make us lunch. When shall we go?
-What about Sunday?
-Okay.
What do you want for lunch?
Sandwiches, rice balls, or bagels?
Anything's fine.
Shout if you find anything! Let's go!
What are they doing?
I'm not really sure, but everyone
was saying something's buried...
Yamada?
Hey! Stop that!
Yamada!
Hey!
-Yamada!
-Get off!
Stop it!
Stop!
Somebody!
Who the fuck are you?
You piece of shit!
-Let's call it a day.
-We'll continue in the morning.
Are you okay?
Evening.
This has gotten out of hand.
Right.
Let's go.
He went out?
Okay.
Oh, my name's Tajima.
No.
Yamada got hurt, so I was worried.
Yes.
Goodbye.
It's fine.
You get that end.
Wakakusa?
Oh, yes.
We won't be able to look at it anymore.
We have no choice.
I'd rather that than have them
treat it like a toy.
Ready, and lift.
Let's dig as deep as we can.
They'll find it if it's shallow.
Right.
Sorry...
My arms and legs are aching.
Timeout. I need to smoke.
Give me one, Wakakusa.
Hey...
What were you thinking when you saw it?
I'm not really sure.
I thought...
"It serves you right."
Yes, "It serves you right."
People pretend to be beautiful,
pretend to be nice,
and pretend to have fun.
It makes me sick.
I may not have one myself,
but you guys don't have a way out either.
So it serves you right.
That's what I thought.
Let's bury it.
Okay.
Let's go.
It's beautiful!
I love fish!
Oh, hey.
Shall we go to Enoshima Aquarium sometime?
They have loads of jellyfish!
They're see-through and so pretty.
They look like frilly dresses!
Haruna...
Oh, Kiteretsu!
My first kiss!
Wobbly, wobbly jelly!
Isn't that Yoshikawa from our school?
Wobbly, wobbly
I bet she got some good money for that.
Very nice.
Wobbly, wobbly jelly!
Things aren't that simple.
A model only needs a nice body.
It's not fair.
It's delicious!
Marry me!
Yes.
You're lucky, Kannonzaki.
What?
You don't seem to have
a care in the world.
Yes.
Let's go after Kiteretsu is done.
Seriously? You're not staying?
I'm not.
Sorry, I have plans later.
Okay.
See you tomorrow, then.
The lunch was delicious.
Thank you, I had fun.
Scary.
Hey, you there.
Will you stop taking
every carton of milk we have?
What are you doing? Can't you knock first?
Is this all that's left?
I wanted to make pudding.
Get out! Don't just come in here!
I will, if you stop going into my room.
I know you do that.
If you touch my diary again,
I'll get Mom to put a lock on the door.
Oh, one more thing.
Will you stop wearing my clothes
without asking me?
It stretches them.
Yamada.
What is it?
I thought I'd give the cats some milk.
Do you have class?
-I skipped it.
-Okay.
They've grown.
Yes.
They looked like little mice
when you first found them.
Here.
He's greedy.
And again!
To me!
You like him, right?
How did you know?
Yoshikawa told me.
Yes, I do.
Don't you want to tell him you like him?
I do.
Or that you want him to hold you?
-Yes.
-To kiss you?
-Of course.
-And sex?
I really want to.
Do you take it or give it, Yamada?
How do you decide when it's two men?
Doesn't it hurt when it goes in?
I guess you use lube like in the books?
Do you prefer having your clitoris
licked or fingered?
What?
Do you spit or swallow?
It's rude to ask me about sex
just because I'm gay.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
Rather than any of that stuff...
just being with him would be enough.
He's there.
I'm there.
And I can see him.
That would be enough.
Heard in the day
Lull'd by the moonlight
Have all passed away
Beautiful dreamer, queen of my song
List while I woo thee with soft melody
Gone are the cares of life's busy throng
Beautiful dreamer, awake unto me
What is it?
Come to my place today.
What's with you?
Do you have the stuff?
No.
I won't come, then.
Don't say things like that.
Isn't Haruna giving you any?
What?
Hey.
My period's late.
What will you do?
How did you meet
your 38-year-old boyfriend?
A friend introduced us.
A friend?
Yes, someone I met at a club somewhere.
What do you like about him?
His money.
Do your parents know about him?
No, they don't!
He's 38 and married, after all.
There's no way I'd introduce him to them.
My parents trust me.
When are you conscious
of your physical body?
When I'm having sex.
What does love mean to you?
Love?
MIYASHITA, CONDOM. NAKAMURA, CAME INSIDE.
KANNONZAKI, CAME INSIDE. EISUKE, CONDOM.
NOGUCHI, DON'T REMEMBER.
SHIBUYA DUDE, CONDOM.
IKEBUKURO CLUB DUDE, CAME INSIDE.
YOSHIKAWA, CONDOM.
Rumi!
Get in the bath!
Okay!
Haruna, answer it!
What?
Answer the phone!
Okay!
Hello, Wakakusa residence.
Hello?
What happened?
They hung up.
-Was it tasty?
-Yes.
I'm glad!
-Can I make you something again?
-Yes.
Don't worry, I like cooking.
-What do you like?
-Whatever.
Hey, shall we take lunch
to an aquarium again?
Yes.
I bought a CD earlier
that I thought you'd like.
I'll lend it to you!
I also bought some blue wool.
It's absolutely beautiful.
I thought I'd knit you a sweater.
I think blue suits you.
Do you like blue? You could wear it
and we could go on a date.
Where shall we go?
I'd like to go see Original Love live.
They have a gig coming up
at Shibuya Club Quattro.
Hopefully, we can get tickets!
And there's an interesting exhibition
on at that art gallery in Omori.
I'd love to go there together!
-Then there's--
-Shut up!
Yamada?
Do you enjoy talking about pointless crap?
About things you want me to do?
Do you love talking about
nothing but yourself?
I went to the bushes,
but something was different.
Though it's all quiet now.
Has something happened?
No, nothing.
Okay.
-Wakakusa.
-Yes?
Let's try calling a UFO.
I've done it before, just once.
How should I do it?
Do it in your head.
It's freezing!
-I know, right?
-Is my fringe weird?
-No, it's fine.
-Thanks.
Rumi!
-Hi!
-Morning!
Are you okay now?
You were gone for three days,
we were worried!
This year's colds really drag on.
-I'm glad you're better.
-A letter!
-What?
-A love letter?
-Who's it from?
Doesn't say.
Open it!
Who is it? I can't wait!
YOU'RE BETTER OFF DEAD
How creepy.
Forget about it!
-Haruna! Morning!
-Morning.
Are you okay now, Koyama?
Yes.
Hey, Haruna.
Do you think I should get a haircut?
-Or should I grow it out?
-I don't care.
-What should I do?
-Whatever!
-Which one?
-Move.
-Which?
-Enough already!
-Which is better?
-I don't care!
You're skipping class.
Period pain.
Only kidding.
Come here for a minute.
-I found something interesting.
-What?
You'll see, come on!
-One second.
-It's fine.
Hey!
Yoshikawa!
Wakakusa!
-This way!
-What is it?
What? What is it?
Over there.
Here.
Take a look.
Isn't it crazy?
I think it's a cat or something.
It looks like meatballs!
I'm sorry, Wakakusa.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Please don't cry.
Nice and loud!
Three, four, five, six,
seven, eight...
What a beautiful color!
Is it a present?
Yamada likes blue.
That's so nice!
He doesn't shut up about
wanting me to knit for him!
-That's so nice!
-I envy you!
-It's so cool that you can knit!
-You're really good!
-That will really suit him!
-Right!
It's so cute!
How lovely!
What's this about? It's freezing.
You'd fuck me if we were indoors.
Or maybe you don't mind being outside?
What does that mean?
All you think about is sex.
I asked if you had
the stuff earlier, right?
What are you talking about?
Give me money.
What?
For the operation.
How much?
It's 150,000.
What?
There's no way it costs that much.
Well, it does.
Is it really mine?
Why didn't you use protection?
It wasn't just when we were high,
you've never used at all!
Even though you use one with Haruna!
I don't have that kind of money.
You said you'd get cash for the stuff.
I've run out.
But you still have money
to buy Haruna a present?
All right.
But I can't give you all of it.
Haruna doesn't like you at all.
What do you mean?
She told me.
"I don't like Kannonzaki at all.
He's a dumbass.
He gets pissed
when I don't let him fuck me."
I don't like you at all, either.
Shut your mouth.
Even your parents
don't care about you, right?
-They totally neglect you!
-Stop it.
-What can you do? You're nothing.
You're a piece of shit, bullying thief
who fucks his girlfriend's friend!
And who's the father of that brat?
You're a piece of shit!
Violence again!
Because nobody likes you!
-Because nobody loves you!
-Stop it!
Are your feelings hurt?
What a dumbass!
Stop it...
Incredible.
It's my mom's hobby.
It looks like a love hotel.
-Are you hungry?
-Oh, yes.
I've ordered some food.
Sit down.
-Would you like some wine?
-Yes.
I might be quitting school.
Really?
Yes.
I'm going to be a regular
on three TV shows.
I worked hard in my freshman year,
but sophomore might not be so good.
I wanted to go to college.
I won't be able to eat all this.
Don't worry, I will.
You're joking.
It's fine. I'll throw it up after anyway.
Would you like a coffee?
Sure.
Thanks.
Do you hate me now, Wakakusa?
Not at all.
I like you, Wakakusa.
We'll buy gloves in a convenience store.
Don't tell anybody!
Anybody!
-I'll kill you if you do.
-What will you do?
Come on, let's go.
It takes ages to bury someone.
Oh, yes.
-I'll call two more people.
-What?
We've dug together before,
so it's perfect.
Who?
Wakakusa and Yoshikawa.
What's going on with you and Haruna?
Nothing.
I have no sexual interest in girls.
And you don't have to worry about
being with me. I hate you.
Okay.
Okay. Okay, got it.
What is it?
It was Yamada.
He said he found a new dead body!
He wants us to go see it now
before he buries it.
What do you mean?
NO TRESPASSING
What are you doing?
That's not yours to look at!
Fuck you!
You frustrated, ugly bitch!
What have you been doing?
You're such an idiot!
A child you don't know who the father is?
What will you do?
"I got 50,000 just for having sex once."
That's prostitution!
It's none of your business!
Shut up, you pig!
Get out, you ugly bitch!
Stop writing your gay manga!
Try getting yourself a boyfriend!
Lose some weight, fatty!
You pig!
Die!
Hey!
What's going on? You're being so loud...
Haruna!
Where is it?
-It went off somewhere.
-What?
It was here a minute ago.
I see.
That sucks.
I'm sorry. That's not right.
Koyama and I weren't like that.
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
Hello.
Is Ichiro home?
Okay, I see.
Hello.
Is Haruna there?
Die.
I'm sorry.
Let's head off.
Wakakusa.
What's with you two?
What kind of relationship is this?
What kind...
-Surely not you and Yamada?
-I told you we're not!
Then what?
Don't make fun of me, Yamada!
-If only you weren't around...
-Stop it, Kannonzaki!
You're the person I like more than anyone!
I'm sorry I couldn't say
that until now. I'm sorry!
-I won't leave you alone again!
-Haruna!
-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Let's leave the idiot here.
But what about Wakakusa?
She'll be fine.
It has nothing to do with her.
So she'll be fine.
This is Wakakusa's.
From when we dug that hole.
Haruna!
Haruna...
How long have you been dating Yamada?
Since December last year.
I like Ozawa who used
to be in Flipper's Guitar.
I was listening to his first solo album
in the Shibuya HMV,
and Yamada was nearby,
also listening to it.
I knew who he was,
but we were in different classes,
but I thought he had
such a beautiful face.
There's something special about Yamada.
He dresses so well,
he has a sort of mysterious vibe,
and he's just kind of different
from the other rough boys.
But I thought it would be a mistake
to talk to him at school,
so I thought I'd talk to him there.
We went straight to a café
on Spain-zaka together,
and from there I started
to lend him all kinds of CDs.
Then, at Christmas,
I plucked up the courage
to ask him to be my boyfriend,
and he just said "Okay"!
I really couldn't believe
that it had happened.
I was so happy.
And now you're happy, right?
Yes, I am.
Really happy.
Well...
Do you ever think to yourself
you're happy to be alive?
I'm happy to be alive.
The snow that falls on top of Mount Fuji
And the snow that falls
On Ponto-cho in Kyoto
They're both the same snow, aren't they?
Once they're thawed, everyone's the same
-Hey.
-Yes?
Lots of crazy shit has happened
at school lately, hasn't it?
Sure has.
You know, it's because in the Edo period,
they used to execute people there.
For real?
And, it's been seen recently.
What has?
Kanna Tajima's ghost.
That's not funny.
That was crazy.
I bet she was trying to set
Wakakusa's apartment on fire.
Then she caught fire!
It's Yamada's fault.
Yamada's crazy, isn't he?
He is.
Jeez.
He scares me.
Rumi had a baby.
Yes.
I didn't know she has a big sister either.
Right.
I don't think we could
have done anything...
But I wish she told us.
Are you really moving?
Yes.
My mom said it's hard
living in the apartment block.
And my room was burned to a crisp.
I see.
Okay.
Haruna!
Shall we have a coffee break in a minute?
Sure.
We've got more luggage than I expected.
I don't have much.
It's because we threw
the fire extinguisher out.
I still hadn't paid off the turntable.
What can you do?
Yes!
-Hi! I came to help out.
-Okay.
Hey.
Do you have any attachment to the town?
I'm not sure.
What's happening to you and Kannonzaki?
I don't think I'll ever see him again.
I think he will be relieved once I'm gone.
You're a lifesaver!
-Keep it up!
-You got it!
Do you feel sad at all?
What do you mean by "sad"?
Like you've lost something
precious to you.
Well then I guess I'm not sad, I think.
Do you feel like you're alive?
If I had to say...
I don't feel alive.
What do you mean by that?
Because I don't change.
You don't change?
Yes, like a stone...
or plastic.
I guess I'm like them
because I don't change much.
So what do you think it means to be alive?
Feeling things, I think.
Feeling the warmth of warm things,
or the coldness of cold things...
That's what I think it is.
Recently...
there was a day
that a lot of stuff happened.
Kanna Tajima died...
and Rumi...
lost
her baby.
I don't know if it's appropriate...
to use the word "felt".
But even though I never even knew
that it existed...
I felt like I'd lost someone
for the first time in my life.
But will you go on living life?
I want to live my life.
How will you live your life?
Wounded.
Forgetting.
Remembering.
Sometimes crying,
sometimes getting angry...
Sometimes smiling and laughing.
I want to live my life feeling things.
I want to live my life.
I have school tomorrow
so I won't be able to see you off.
See you.
Thank you.
Take care.
See you.
Goodnight.
Wakakusa.
Yamada.
Here. Maybe you could take this with you.
What is it?
It has my favorite poem
of William Gibson in it.
-William?
-William Gibson.
Thank you.
Shall we go for a little walk?
Okay.
What's up?
Nothing.
It was very sudden, wasn't it?
Well...
It's just an early spring break.
-"This city, in plague time,
-knew our brief eternity.
-Our brief eternity,
-our love.
-Our love knew...
-the blank walls at street level.
-Our love knew the frequency of silence.
-Our love knew...
-the flat field.
-We became field operators,
-we sought to decode the lattices.
-To phase-shift to new alignments,
-to patrol the deep faults,
-to map the flow.
-Look at the leaves...
-how they circle in the dry fountain.
-How we survive in the flat field."
Recently...
Yes?
I saw Tajima's ghost.
What?
Maybe it was my imagination.
But I think I saw her at school.
You think?
To put it more accurately,
I sensed, not saw her.
Like she was just there,
not doing anything.
But it doesn't bother me.
I like her more...
when she's dead than when she's alive.
But I wish I liked her more
when she was still alive.
Do you...
not like people unless they're dead?
That's not it.
I like her.
Is that right?
Besides...
you're alive, and I like you.
I mean it.
I'm going to miss you when you're gone.
Wakakusa.
Let's try calling a UFO one more time.
Let's try again.
由我编辑和重新同步# NAIM2007 #
你的泰迪熊怎么了？
这个？
好吧，我爸爸买了这只熊
当我三岁。
不是我记得的，
这正是我妈妈说的。
他在休息区买的
当我们去旅行的时候。
我一直...
父亲买了这个，但那不是
我养这只熊的原因。
毛绒玩具很难
扔进垃圾桶，对吧？
他们有眼睛！
她有名字吗？
是的。
顾。
就这样。
她有一张可爱的脸，对吧？
学校...
你在哪里？
山田？
我是特快列车上的工程师
每个车站都有漂亮的女孩
但当你只停留三分钟时
没有足够的时间亲吻他们
-东京、京都、大阪
-嘿。
是的？
你知道广告
和牧濑里穗在海里？
是的。
显然有一张女人的脸
在水里。
-真正的？
-真正的。
这是一个溺水妇女的鬼魂。
什么？真正的？
- 可怕，对吧？
-是的！
显然你可以看到它
如果你暂停视频。
-没门！
-这是真的。
没门！看到了吗，高桥？
-什么，我？
-是的。
我想我看到了。
-真正的？
-是的。
这太可怕了。
-这是正确的？
-是的！
-若草。
-是的？
你闻不到海的味道吗？
我们镇上有一条河。
它靠近河口，
水散开并停滞不前。
味道不好。
加拿大一枝黄花生长在河边，
而且你会经常看到死猫
周边地区。
不得擅自闯入
波奇！
你在哪里？
该回家了。
波奇！
玩过吗？
哦，你有东西。
你找到好东西了吗？
你发现了什么？
正确的。
来吧，波奇。
该走了。
好的，波奇！
好的。
我们回家吧。
鲁米！
这就是兰蔻 Définicils！
是的。
我找了人给我买。
我希望我的男朋友是 38 岁！
让高桥给你买一个。
就像那样会发生！
耀西！
榛名！昨天还好吗？
乌戈乌戈鲁加
到家的时候已经结束了。
我妈妈生我的气。
哦，还有观音崎。
什么？
早晨！
我不知道观音崎和榛名如何
目前正在做。
不要问我。
她把事情留给自己太多了。
她甚至没有说他们在一起。
虽然他很热！
我受不了观音崎。
榛名对男人没有品味。
-你个混蛋！
-好痛。
-山田和储物柜！
-它是什么？
你太可怕了！
什么？
你怎么知道？
-Yoshie 告诉我的。
-高桥？
太可怕了！
漆黑一片，冰冷的……
-你去帮助他？
-我当然做了！
再做类似的事情
我会杀了你！
什么？
你和山田有什么关系吗？
别傻了！
是田岛环奈。
也许她在找山田。
他还没来！
嘿。
-早晨。
或许传闻并不属实。
-什么？
- 那个山田的同性恋。
有人在新宿见过他，
和一个男孩手牵手。
我听说他和大一新生在一起
吉川小泽。
你是说那个模特儿？
显然他们去了灌木丛
一起在河边。
我打赌你是从高桥那里听说的。
他所说的一切都不是真的。
嘿，这很卑鄙！
-停下来！
-今天来我家吧。
没人在家。
在你的梦里，笨蛋！
吃多少就吃多少。
你也是，普纳。
早安，丸！
你一定是困了。
怎么了？
你有一双漂亮的眼睛，不是吗？
关于公民自由，
有良心自由，
身体自由，经济自由。
良心自由意味着自由
随心所欲地思考和说话。
宗教信仰，人们的聚会，
表达方式，
学习之类的不是
受国家限制，
个人自由必须得到保护。
这个原则
是基于国家的控制
战前的神道教，
并且它的持续性受到深切关注。
现在，言论自由...
别惹我。
这意味着给予的权利
你对别人的看法...
请告诉我们您的姓名。
我是观音崎
很高兴见到你。
你家中有多少成员？
有我的爸爸，我的妈妈，
我的大哥，还有我。
我的亲密家庭。
你的近亲？
我爸妈没在一起
我想你可以说
他们不关心彼此。
她发现他出轨了，
这是同一个老故事。
我妈妈喜欢跳舞，
她整个星期什么都没做。
我爸爸和他办公室的一个女人...
我说“女人”，但她大约 45 岁，
她实际上是一个奶奶。
他们一起逃跑了
去年秋天左右，
但他们回来了
大约一周后结束。
现在一切正常。
我们都表现得好像什么都没发生一样。
你女朋友知道吗
关于你的家人？
不，我还没有和她谈过这件事。
为什么不？
我不认为她会感兴趣
在这样的事情中，
而她身边只有她妈妈，
所以她可能会嫉妒我
因为有两个父母。
你们两个是怎么开始见面的？
我想这感觉不错。
她有时真的很生气，
但她不会太怀疑，
所以她很容易相处。
闭上你的嘴！
跳闸。
剥什么？
我叫你脱！
跳闸！
-Haruna的逃课！
-我头疼。
我饿死了。
我敢打赌你又想要那个粗乌冬面了。
-现在是我的最爱！
-没门！
这是一场纸质暴风雪！
哇！
太奇妙了！
山田一郎
-怪异的！你看到了吗？
-我认同。
真正的？
-嘿！
-观音崎在哪里？
- 他说他今天下午要逃课。
-山田在哪里？
-我不知道。
-你在撒谎！
这是什么？
那家伙疯了。
我们只是在胡闹。
你是什么意思？
做一点事。
这是只有女朋友才能说的。
山田在哪里？
老化学实验室。
不得擅自闯入
山田！
没关系。
是若草。
我带来了你的衣服。你在哪里？
这边。
对不起，又发生了。
没关系。
-若草。
-是的？
你今晚有空吗？
是的。
我会告诉你我的秘密宝藏。
什么？
我想让你看看。
臭氧层消耗率
在过去 17 年中从 5% 上升到 10%。
释放的碳氟化合物量
人类进入大气层
是 1500 万吨。
大约 10%，150 万吨，
到达平流层，
破坏臭氧层。
妈妈，我要和一个朋友见面，
锅里有咖喱，哈鲁娜
对不起！
轮到我做饭了。
你小时候是什么样的？
上小学的时候，
我总是去图书馆。
我喜欢关于不明飞行物的书。
我一直想看一个。
我从小学开始就被欺负了。
有一天，我被打得很惨。
我的整个身体都是黑色和蓝色，
我不能让我父母知道。
让你的父母发现是最糟糕的。
所以...
我不想回家。
我从屋顶仰望天空
直到天黑。
我一直希望有一个不明飞行物出现。
我想我在那里呆了几个小时。
我仍然感到强烈的愿望
时不时去看一个。
它不一定是不明飞行物。
我猜...
我想完全看一些东西
不同于现实的出现。
你好，小山家。
给你打电话。有个叫观音崎的男孩。
好的。
不要再打长电话了。
妈妈说你让她付出代价--
好的。
它是什么？
什么？
那太残忍了。
每个人都讨厌我。
这不是真的。
我敢打赌，有些女孩喜欢你。
他们认为你可爱或神秘——
我不是那样的好人。
我想毁了人们
谁把我当成虫子，
把他们的皮肤翻过来，加盐，
并将其喂给狗。
我想把垃圾丢进嘴里
那些看着和笑的女孩。
这就是我一直在想的。
我是同性恋。
你可以叫我同性恋，基佬，
变态，什么的。
但是你没有看到B班的田岛吗？
那只是一种行为。
田岛知道吗？
不。
这对她不公平，真的。
你是第一个正常人
我曾经说过，若草。
真的没事吗？
没关系。
我妈妈在上舞蹈课，
我爸爸出差了。
另外我会生气
如果我们今天做不到。
太自私了。
来的女孩说
一通电话后。
快点把它拿出来。
你在开玩笑吧，一条蛇？不，这不对...
它就在这附近的某个地方。
什么？
-这里是。
-什么？
你做这种事吗
和榛名也一样？
住口。这不关你的事。
我是去年发现的。
我像今天一样被殴打。
很尴尬，所以我来这里哭了。
然后我看到了这个。
-你告诉警察了吗？
-我真的应该，但是...
去年秋天前后，
骨头上还有肉。
我们去吧。
我...
不知道我是死是活……
但看着它给了我勇气。
不，我会死……
我会死...
另一个人知道这件事。
谁？
吉川小泽。
新生？
去年年底来的时候，
她已经在这里了。
从那时起，我们有时会聚在一起。
也是她的宝物。
你做了多久了
这种工作？
也许从我大约三岁开始。
一开始我不是模特
我更像一个儿童演员。
我做过戏剧之类的事情
和电视广告。
我的父母从事这一行，
所以他们问我是否想尝试这样做。
但就作品本身而言，
每个人都聚在一起做一件事
我认为这很棒。
当你做杂志工作时，
你和摄影师一起工作
和各种各样的人。
而且还有更多优秀的人
当你做电视工作时。
但你会感觉到
不一定是你。
任何人都可以做到。
你认为任何人都能做到吗？
我觉得我看到的时候看起来很恶心
一本杂志或我喜欢的东西。
我想知道他们为什么一直使用我
带着丑陋的脸，
还夸我。
但我不相信他们。
我确定真相
是不是他们真的不是这个意思
他们只是说
他们认为他们必须说的话。
就像他们对自己很满意
因为把丑陋的人称为美丽。
学校怎么样？你喜欢吗？
与工作相比，学校感觉很真实。
正版？
不知道学校里的人有没有
按原样称呼事物，
但我敢肯定，如果他们认为
有些事情很丑，他们会说出来。
他们至少会在你背后说出来。
- 你的意思是每个人都是诚实的？
-是的。
吉川，你感觉如何？
我会去我的下一堂课。
那不行。
你需要有一个均衡的饮食。
您的健康先于工作。
是的，护士。
所以年长的学生也经常逃课。
你有足够的学分吗？
我很想念学校的工作，
所以我只有足够的。
哦，看。
刚刚扔球的那个。
向中心跑去。
是的！
那是山田喜欢的人。
什么？
那个男孩...
他是山田的另一宝。
我穿着我的海军制服
我是东京巴士女郎
-嘿。
-是的？
化了妆的老太太
从学校附近的公寓...
是的？
她擦干她的透视，
在阳台上系上紫色内裤。
那个老太太拿走了樱桃
我们学校的无数男孩。
真正的？
你为什么不问她？
不过，她几岁了？
- 之后再问。
-好的。
哦，有什么东西在咬人！
-你个傻冒。
-拉屎！
-你是说？
-正确的。
-你知道学校后面的河吗？
-是的？
嗯，那里...
打扰一下！
嘿！
你有没有听见过？
老人死了，他的钱被埋了，
我们可能...
-你在说什么？
-所以无论如何！
灌木丛中有一间小屋，
靠近学校后面的河边。
一个老人住在那里，对吧？
他被驱逐了，他搬家了
到不同的公寓，
但他最近去世了。
他死时身无分文，
但他藏了很多钱！
真的吗？
你猜怎么着！
钱被埋在灌木丛中！
-灌木丛？
-正确的！
千万在灌木丛中！
是不是很神奇？
一秒钟，我只是...
榛名！
-多少钱？
-140 日元。
吉川在吗？
吉川？
她之前来过这里，但是……
她经常消失。
什么？
一千万！
你能用它做什么？
- 榛名在哪里？
- 她去了某个地方。
正确的。
我可以让我的梦想成真！
千万日元！
你为什么把我带到这里来？
我还在生你气。
为什么？
也许我会把一切都告诉Haruna。
什么？
你如何捆绑我的手脚，
蒙住我的眼睛，
并粘了一罐慕斯
在我的两个洞里！
你这个小...
嘿！
我只是在开玩笑。
嘿...
我们在这里做吗？
-你想要一亿日元吗？
-是的！
-你想变得肮脏富有吗？
‫ !Money-‬‬
‫ Money-‬‬
-真是一群白痴！
‫ !Money-‬‬
我只是说有可能
把钱埋在那里。
什么？这不是真的？
我妈妈去参加老人的葬礼，
她想知道
如果他可能把它埋了。
什么？
那1.5亿呢？
你从哪里得到那个的？
是真的吗，高桥？
好吧，我们走吧！
-我们走吧！
等待！
这不是真的！
嘿！
钱是骗人的！
这是一个谎言！
这是一个谎言！嘿！
这不是真的！嘿！
榛名！
你要去哪里？
那些小混混。
嘿。你要去哪里？
-来吧。
-嘿。
我会告诉你我的秘密宝藏。
对不起。
我以为这真的很适合你。
你看起来像一个蓝色的人。
我什么都没给你
为了你的生日。
我们十二月才开始约会，
你的生日在三月。
谢谢你。
你想去吗
去八景岛的水族馆？
我还没有去过那里。
当然。
我给我们做午饭。我们什么时候去？
-星期天呢？
-好的。
你想要什么午餐？
三明治、饭团还是百吉饼？
什么都好。
发现什么就喊！我们走吧！
他们在做什么？
我不是很确定，但每个人
说有什么东西被埋了……
山田？
嘿！不要那么做！
山田！
嘿！
-山田！
-下车！
停下来！
停止！
有人！
你他妈是谁？
你个狗屎！
-让我们收工。
-我们将在早上继续。
你还好吗？
晚上。
这已经失控了。
正确的。
我们走吧。
他出去了？
好的。
哦，我叫田岛。
不。
山田受伤了，我很担心。
是的。
再见。
没关系。
你得到那个结果。
若草？
哦是的。
我们将无法再看它。
我们别无选择。
我宁愿那样也不愿拥有它们
把它当作玩具。
准备好，举起。
让我们尽可能深入地挖掘。
如果它很浅，他们会找到它。
正确的。
对不起...
我的胳膊和腿都在痛。
暂停。我需要抽烟。
给我一个，若草。
嘿...
你看到的时候在想什么？
我不太确定。
我想...
“它对你有用。”
是的，“它对你有用。”
人们假装美丽，
假装好看，
并假装玩得很开心。
这让我感到恶心。
我自己可能没有，
但你们也没有出路。
所以它为你服务。
我也那么认为。
让我们把它埋起来。
好的。
我们走吧。
很美丽！
我爱鱼！
噢！嗨。
有时间去江之岛水族馆好吗？
他们有很多水母！
它们是透明的，非常漂亮。
它们看起来像褶边连衣裙！
榛名...
哦，Kiteretsu！
我的初吻！
摇摇晃晃的果冻！
不是我们学校的吉川吗？
摇摇晃晃，摇摇晃晃
我敢打赌她为此赚了一些钱。
非常好。
摇摇晃晃的果冻！
事情没那么简单。
模特只需要好身材。
这不公平。
很好吃！
嫁给我吧！
是的。
你很幸运，观音崎。
什么？
你好像没有
世界上的一种关怀。
是的。
Kiteretsu 完成后我们再去吧。
严重地？你不留下来？
我不是。
对不起，我以后有计划。
好的。
那么明天见。
午餐很好吃。
谢谢你，我玩得很开心。
害怕。
你在吗。
你会停止服用吗
我们拥有的每一盒牛奶？
你在做什么？你不能先敲门吗？
这就是剩下的吗？
我想做布丁。
出去！不要只是进来！
我会的，如果你停止进入我的房间。
我知道你这样做。
如果你再碰我的日记，
我会让妈妈把门锁上。
哦，还有一件事。
你会停止穿我的衣服吗
不问我？
它伸展它们。
山田。
它是什么？
我想我会给猫一些牛奶。
你有课吗？
-我跳过了。
-好的。
他们长大了。
是的。
他们看起来像小老鼠
当你第一次找到它们时。
这里。
他很贪婪。
然后再次！
大部头书！
你喜欢他，对吧？
你怎么知道？
吉川告诉我。
是的，我愿意。
你不想告诉他你喜欢他吗？
我愿意。
还是你想让他抱你？
-是的。
-来吻你？
-当然。
- 和性？
我真的很想。
是拿还是给，山田？
你怎么决定什么时候是两个男人？
进去的时候不疼吗？
我猜你像书中那样使用润滑油？
你喜欢有你的阴蒂吗
舔或手指？
什么？
你吐还是吞？
问我关于性的问题很不礼貌
只是因为我是同性恋。
对不起。
不，没关系。
而不是那些东西...
只要和他在一起就足够了。
他在那里。
我在那里。
我可以看到他。
那就足够了。
当天听到
被月光迷住了
都过世了
美丽的梦想家，我的歌后
当我用柔和的旋律向你求爱时列出来
生活忙碌的人群的烦恼已经一去不复返了
美丽的梦想家，醒醒我
它是什么？
今天来我家。
你怎么了？
你有东西吗？
不。
那我就不来了
不要说那样的话。
春菜不给你吗？
什么？
嘿。
我的月经来晚了。
你会怎么做？
你是怎么认识的
你38岁的男朋友？
一位朋友介绍我们。
一个朋友？
是的，我在某个俱乐部遇到的人。
你喜欢他什么？
他的钱。
你父母知道他吗？
不，他们没有！
毕竟，他已经 38 岁了，已经结婚了。
我不可能把他介绍给他们。
我的父母信任我。
你什么时候有意识
你的身体？
当我做爱时。
爱对你意味着什么？
爱？
宫下，避孕套。中村，进来了。
神野崎，进来了。荣介，避孕套。
野口，不记得了。
涩谷哥们，避孕套。
池袋俱乐部老兄，进来了。
吉川，避孕套。
鲁米！
去洗澡吧！
好的！
哈鲁纳，回答吧！
什么？
接电话！
好的！
你好，若草宅邸。
你好？
发生了什么？
他们挂断了电话。
-好吃吗？
-是的。
我很高兴！
-我可以再给你做点什么吗？
-是的。
别担心，我喜欢做饭。
-你喜欢什么？
-任何。
嘿，我们吃午饭好吗
再去水族馆？
是的。
我之前买了一张CD
我以为你会喜欢的。
我借给你！
我还买了一些蓝色羊毛。
这绝对是美丽的。
我以为我会给你织一件毛衣。
我觉得蓝色适合你。
你喜欢蓝色吗？你可以穿
我们可以去约会。
我们应该去哪里？
我想去现场看Original Love。
他们即将举行一场演出
在涩谷俱乐部 Quattro。
希望我们能买到票！
还有一个有趣的展览
在大森的那个美术馆。
我很想一起去那里！
-然后有--
-住口！
山田？
你喜欢谈论毫无意义的废话吗？
关于你想让我做的事情？
你喜欢谈论
除了你自己什么都没有？
我去了灌木丛，
但有些不同。
虽然现在一切都很平静。
有什么事吗？
没什么。
好的。
-若草。
-是的？
让我们试着叫一个不明飞行物。
我以前做过，只有一次。
我该怎么做？
在你的脑海里做。
它冻结！
-我知道，对吧？
-我的边缘很奇怪吗？
-不，还好。
-谢谢。
鲁米！
-你好！
-早晨！
你现在好吗？
你走了三天，
我们很担心！
今年的感冒真的拖了。
-我很高兴你变得更好了。
-一封信！
-什么？
- 一封情书？
-是谁寄来的？
不说。
打开它！
是谁？我等不及了！
你最好死了
多么令人毛骨悚然。
忘掉它！
-榛名！早晨！
-早晨。
你现在还好吗，小山？
是的。
嘿，哈鲁娜。
你觉得我应该理发吗？
-或者我应该把它长出来吗？
-我不在乎。
-我应该怎么办？
-任何！
-哪一个？
-移动。
-哪个？
-已经足够！
-哪个更好？
-我不在乎！
你逃课了。
经期痛。
只是在开玩笑。
来这里一分钟。
-我发现了一些有趣的东西。
-什么？
你会看到的，加油！
-一秒。
-没关系。
嘿！
吉川！
若草！
-这边走！
-它是什么？
什么？它是什么？
在那边。
这里。
看一看。
这不是疯了吗？
我觉得是猫什么的。
看起来像肉丸子！
对不起，若草。
我不是故意的。
嘿。
对不起。
请不要哭泣。
好听又好听！
三，四，五，六，
七八...
多么美丽的颜色！
是礼物吗？
山田喜欢蓝色。
太好了！
他没有闭嘴
要我给他织毛衣！
-太好了！
-我羡慕你！
- 你可以织毛衣，太酷了！
-你真的很棒！
——那真的很适合他！
-正确的！
它真可爱！
多么可爱！
这是怎么回事？它冻结。
如果我们在室内，你会操我的。
或者你不介意在外面？
这意味着什么？
你所想的只是性。
我问你有没有
之前的东西，对吧？
你在说什么？
给我钱。
什么？
对于操作。
多少钱？
这是150,000。
什么？
没办法花那么多钱。
嗯，确实如此。
真的是我的吗？
为什么不使用保护？
不只是在我们高高在上的时候，
你根本没用过！
即使你和榛名一起使用！
我没有那种钱。
你说你会得到现金的东西。
我已经用完了。
但你还有钱
给榛名买礼物？
好的。
但我不能给你全部。
哈鲁纳根本不喜欢你。
你是什么意思？
她告诉我。
“我一点也不喜欢观音崎。
他是个笨蛋。
他生气了
当我不让他操我的时候。”
我也不喜欢你。
闭上你的嘴。
甚至你的父母
不在乎你，对吧？
- 他们完全忽视了你！
-停下来。
-你能做什么？你什么都不是。
你是一坨屎，欺负小偷
谁操他女朋友的朋友！
那小子的父亲又是谁？
你就是一坨屎！
又是暴力！
因为没人喜欢你！
-因为没有人爱你！
-停下来！
你的感情受伤了吗？
真是个笨蛋！
停下来...
极好的。
这是我妈妈的爱好。
它看起来像一个情人酒店。
-你饿了吗？
-哦是的。
我点了一些食物。
坐下。
-你想喝点酒吗？
-是的。
我可能要退学了。
真的吗？
是的。
我要成为常客
在三个电视节目中。
大一的时候我很努力，
但大二可能没那么好。
我想上大学。
这一切我都吃不完。
别担心，我会的。
你在开玩笑么。
没关系。反正以后我会扔的。
你想喝咖啡吗？
当然。
谢谢。
你现在恨我吗，若草？
一点也不。
我喜欢你，若草。
我们会在便利店买手套。
不要告诉任何人！
任何人！
-如果你这样做，我会杀了你。
-你会怎么做？
来吧，我们走吧。
埋葬一个人需要很长时间。
哦是的。
-我再叫两个人。
-什么？
我们以前一起挖过，
所以它是完美的。
谁？
若草和吉川。
你和春菜怎么了？
没有什么。
我对女孩没有性兴趣。
而且您不必担心
和我在一起。我恨你。
好的。
好的。好，知道了。
它是什么？
是山田。
他说他发现了一具新的尸体！
他要我们现在去看
在他埋葬之前。
你是什么意思？
不得擅自闯入
你在做什么？
那不是你要看的！
你沮丧，丑陋的婊子！
你都干了什么？
你真是个白痴！
一个不知道父亲是谁的孩子？
你会怎么做？
“我仅仅因为做爱一次就得到了50,000。”
那是卖淫！
这不关你的事！
闭嘴，猪！
滚开，你这个丑陋的婊子！
别再写你的同性恋漫画了！
试着给自己找个男朋友！
减肥吧，胖子！
你个猪！
死！
嘿！
这是怎么回事？你声音太大了...
榛名！
它在哪里？
- 它在某处发生了。
-什么？
一分钟前就在这里。
我懂了。
太糟糕了。
对不起。那是不对的。
小山和我不是这样的。
我很抱歉！
对不起！
你好。
一郎在家吗？
好的，我明白了。
你好。
哈鲁娜在吗？
死。
对不起。
我们走吧。
若草。
你们两个怎么了？
这是一种什么样的关系？
哪一种...
——当然不是你和山田？
-我告诉过你我们不是！
然后呢？
不要取笑我，山田！
-如果你不在身边的话……
——住手，观音崎！
你是我比谁都喜欢的人！
对不起，我不能说
直到现在。对不起！
-我不会再让你一个人了！
-榛名！
-对不起！
对不起！
让我们把白痴留在这里。
但是若草呢？
她会没事的。
这与她无关。
所以她会没事的。
这是若草的。
从我们挖那个洞开始。
榛名！
榛名...
你和山田约会多久了？
从去年12月开始。
我喜欢使用过的小泽
在鳍状肢的吉他。
我在听他的第一张个人专辑
在涩谷HMV，
山田就在附近，
也在听。
我知道他是谁，
但我们在不同的班级，
但我以为他有
这么漂亮的脸。
山田有一些特别之处。
他穿得这么好，
他有一种神秘的气息，
他只是有点不同
来自其他粗鲁的男孩。
但我认为这将是一个错误
在学校和他说话，
所以我想我会在那里和他谈谈。
我们直接去了一家咖啡馆
一起在西班牙-坂上，
从那里我开始
借给他各种CD。
然后，在圣诞节，
我鼓起勇气
求他做我男朋友
他只是说“好吧”！
我真的不敢相信
它已经发生了。
我非常开心。
现在你很幸福，对吧？
我是。
非常开心。
出色地...
你有没有想过自己
你活着开心吗？
我很高兴还活着。
落在富士山上的雪
还有飘落的雪
京都先斗町
它们都是一样的雪，不是吗？
解冻后，每个人都一样
-嘿。
-是的？
发生了很多疯狂的事情
最近在学校，不是吗？
当然有。
你知道，那是因为在江户时代，
他们曾经在那里处决人。
真正的？
而且，最近才看到。
有什么？
田岛环奈的鬼魂。
这不好笑。
那太疯狂了。
我敢打赌她正试图设置
若草的公寓着火了。
然后她就火了！
是山田的错。
山田疯了，不是吗？
他是。
天哪。
他吓到我了。
鲁米生了一个孩子。
是的。
我也不知道她有一个姐姐。
正确的。
我不认为我们可以
做过什么...
但我希望她告诉我们。
你真的动了吗？
是的。
我妈说很难
住在公寓楼里。
我的房间被烧得焦黑。
我懂了。
好的。
榛名！
一会儿我们喝杯咖啡好吗？
当然。
我们的行李比我预期的要多。
我没有多少。
那是因为我们扔了
灭火器出来。
我还没有还清转盘。
你能做什么？
是的！
-你好！我是来帮忙的。
-好的。
嘿。
你对小镇有什么依恋吗？
我不确定。
你和观音崎怎么了？
我想我再也见不到他了。
我想我一走，他就会松一口气。
你是救生员！
-保持！
-你说对了！
你觉得难过吗？
你说的“悲伤”是什么意思？
就像你失去了什么
对你来说很珍贵。
那么我想我并不难过，我想。
你觉得你还活着吗？
如果我不得不说...
我不觉得活着。
你是什么意思？
因为我不改变。
你不改？
是的，就像一块石头……
或塑料。
我想我和他们一样
因为我变化不大。
那么你认为活着意味着什么？
感觉的东西，我想。
感受温暖事物的温暖，
或者冰冷事物的冰冷……
这就是我认为的。
最近...
有一天
发生了很多事情。
田岛环奈死了……
还有鲁米……
丢失的
她的宝贝。
不知道合适不...
使用“感觉”这个词。
但即使我从来不知道
它存在...
我觉得我失去了一个人
这是我生命中的第一次。
但你会继续生活吗？
我要过我的生活。
你将如何过你的生活？
受伤。
忘记。
记住。
有时会哭，
有时会生气...
有时微笑和大笑。
我想过我的生活感觉的东西。
我要过我的生活。
我明天有学校
所以我不能送你走。
再见。
谢谢你。
小心。
再见。
晚安。
若草。
山田。
这里。也许你可以把这个随身携带。
它是什么？
它有我最喜欢的诗
威廉•吉布森在里面。
-威廉？
——威廉•吉布森。
谢谢你。
我们去散散步好吗？
好的。
怎么了？
什么都没有。
很突然，不是吗？
嗯……
这只是一个早春的假期。
-“这座城市，在瘟疫时期，
-知道我们短暂的永恒。
-我们短暂的永恒，
-我们的爱。
-我们的爱知道...
-街道上的空白墙壁。
- 街道上的空白墙。
-我们的爱知道沉默的频率。
-我们的爱知道...
- 平坦的领域。
- 平坦的场地。
-我们成为了现场操作员，
-我们试图解码格子。
- 我们试图解码格子。
-相移到新的对齐方式，
- 相移到新的对齐方式，
-巡查深层断层，
- 巡视深层断层，
- 映射流。
- 映射流程。
-看树叶……
- 看看树叶...
-他们如何在干涸的喷泉中盘旋。
- 他们如何在干涸的喷泉中盘旋。
-我们如何在平地上生存。”
最近...
是的？
我看到了田岛的鬼魂。
什么？
也许这是我的想象。
但我想我在学校见过她。
您认为？
更准确地说，
我感觉到了，没有看到她。
就像她就在那里一样，
什么都不做。
但这并不困扰我。
我更喜欢她...
她死的时候比她活着的时候。
但我希望我更喜欢她
在她还活着的时候。
你...
不喜欢人，除非他们死了？
不是这个。
我喜欢她。
那正确吗？
除了...
你还活着，我喜欢你。
我是认真的。
你走后我会想念你的。
若草。
让我们再叫一次不明飞行物。
让我们再试一次。